pac-10.org 2019-12-11

# 

Privacy Policy
Effective Date: May 26, 2018
The Pac-12 Entities (which includes Pac-12 Enterprises, LLC, Pac-12 Network, LLC, Pac-12 Broadband
Network, LLC, and the Pac-12 Conference) (collectively, “Pac-12”, ”we”, “us” or “our”) is a diversified and
integrated media company dedicated to Pac-12 sports and related content.
This Privacy Policy (“Policy”) describes the information we collect on the sites where this privacy policy is
posted, including Pac-12.com (the “Sites”). This Policy also applies to programs or services operated by us
(or on our behalf) that may be displayed on various online, mobile or other platforms and environments,
including those operated by third parties, which permits us to interact directly with our guests that post this
Policy, including the Pac-12 Now App (“Applications”). We follow this privacy policy in accordance with local
law in the places where we operate. By visiting our Sites and using our Applications, you agree that your
personal information will be handled as described in this Policy, which is incorporated by reference into the
Terms and Conditions the Sites or Applications, as applicable.
          1.        Types of Information We Collect
          2.        Use of Your Information
          3.        Sharing Your Information
          4.        Your Controls and Choices
          5.        What about Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies
          6.        Children and Privacy
          7.        Data Security and Integrity
          8.        Data Transfers, Storage and Processing Globally
          9.        Third Party Links
          10.       Privacy Policy Changes
          11.       Terms and Conditions
          12.       Special Information for California Consumers
          13.       Data Retention
          14.       Special Information for EEA Data Subjects
          15.       Comments and Questions
1.        Types of Information We Collect
Information We Collect Directly From You
We collect information you provide to us when you request products, services or information from us, register
with us, participate in public forums or other activities on our Sites and Applications, respond to customer
surveys, or otherwise interact with us. Generally, we collect information about you directly from you or your
use of our Site, but in some cases we may collect information about you from third parties.
We may collect the following information directly from you:
    Registration information you provide when you download our Applications or create an account at the
     Sites, including your name, zip code, email address, school and sport preference, username and
     password;
    Transaction information you provide when you request information or purchase a product or service from
     us, whether on our Sites or through our Applications, including your postal address, telephone number
     and payment information;
    Information you provide in public forums that we may make available on our Sites and Applications;
    Information sent either one-to-one or within a limited group using our message, chat, post or
     similar functionality, where we are permitted by law to collect this information;
    Information you provide to us when you use our Sites and Applications, our Applications on third-party
     sites or platforms such as social networking sites, or link your profile on a third-party site or platform with
     your registration account;
    Location information when you visit our Sites or use our Applications, including location information
     either provided by a mobile device interacting with one of our Sites or Applications, or associated with
     your IP address, where we are permitted by law to process this information; and
    Usage, viewing and technical data, including your device identifier or IP address, when you visit our
     Sites, use our Applications on third-party sites or platforms or open emails we send, and aggregate

     data such as the total number of users that view content through the Sites or Applications, the type of
     content they are viewing, the length of time spent viewing the content.
User Generated Content
Any information that you post to public areas of our Sites or Applications may be viewable by other visitors to
our Sites. If you post content to public areas of our Sites or Applications, we may collect and use that
information. We are not responsible for the privacy of any information that you choose to post to public areas
of our Sites or Applications or for the accuracy of any information contained in those postings. Any
information that you disclose becomes public information. We cannot prevent such information from being
used in a manner that may violate this Policy, the law or your personal privacy. You should have no
expectation of privacy in the information you post to the Sites or Applications.
Information We Collect About You From Third Parties
We also may collect information, including personally identifiable information, about you from affiliated and
non- affiliated third parties to identify products and services that might be of interest to you. We will follow the
requirements imposed by those parties with respect to use of the information they provide to us.
Information We Collect Automatically
We may use cookies, web beacons, and other automated devices to collect information, including personally
identifiable information, about you when you visit our Sites and Applications and receive emails from us.
Specifically, we may collect the following information about your use of our Sites or Applications via these
technologies: your browser type and operating system; web pages you view; links you click; your IP address;
your mobile device ID; your interaction with the Sites or Applications; length of time you are logged in to our
Sites or Applications; and websites visited before our Sites. Please see the section “What About Cookies and
Other Tracking Devices” below for more information about our use of cookies. We may use the information
gathered through these methods in anonymous or aggregated form to analyze ways to improve our Sites or
Applications. This information also is associated with your username and may be combined with other
information, including personally identifiable information that we collect about you.
Please keep in mind that when you provide information to us on a third-party site or platform (for example, via
our Applications), the information you provide may be separately collected by the third-party site or platform.
The information we collect is covered by this privacy policy and the information the third-party site or platform
collects is subject to the third-party site or platform's privacy practices. Privacy choices you have made on the
third-party site or platform will not apply to our use of the information we have collected directly through our
Applications.
2.        Use of Your Information
We use the information that we gather about you for the following purposes:
    Provide you with the products and services you request;
    Respond to inquiries and requests;
    Communicate with you about your account or transactions with us and send you information about
     features on our Sites and Applications or changes to our policies;
    Send you offers and promotions for our products and services or third-party products and services;
    Conduct contests, sweepstakes and other competitions through our Sites and Applications/
    Personalize content and experiences on our Sites and Applications;
    Provide you with advertising based on your activity on our Sites and Applications and on third-party
     sites and applications;
    Optimize or improve our products, services and operations; and
    Detect, investigate and prevent activities that may violate our policies or be illegal.
    Confirm that the user is an authenticated user for certain TV Everywhere content or other content made
     available through the Pac-12 Now application.
3.        Sharing Your Information
We may share your information, including personally identifiable information, with other users and affiliated and
non- affiliated third parties as described in this section.

    We may disclose the information we collect from you to the Pac-12 Entities and our affiliates and
     subsidiaries to assist us in providing our services to you and for marketing products and services that we
     believe would be of interest to you.
    We may disclose the information we collect from you to third party vendors, service providers, contractors
     or agents who perform functions on our behalf. For example, these providers may help us administer our
     Sites or Applications.
    We may disclose the information we collect from you in connection with the sale of a business, if we are
     acquired by or merged with another company, if substantially all of our assets are transferred to another
     company, or as part of a bankruptcy proceeding, we may transfer the information we have collected from
     you to the acquiring company.
    We may disclose the information we collect from you where we believe it is necessary to investigate,
     prevent or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to
     the safety of any person or violations of our Terms and Conditions or this Policy.
    We may disclose the information we collect from you to enforce our Terms of Use or rules, to protect
     our rights and property and the rights and property of our guests and third parties, or in other cases if
     we believe in good faith that disclosure is required by law.
    We may disclose the information we collect from you in order to comply with the law, a judicial
     proceeding, court order or other legal process, such as in response to a subpoena.
    We may share aggregate or anonymized information about users with third parties for marketing,
     advertising, research or similar purposes. For example, if we display advertisements on behalf of a third
     party, we may share aggregate, demographic information with that third party about the users to whom
     we displayed the advertisements.
4.        Your Controls and Choices
We provide you the ability to exercise certain controls and choices regarding our collection, use and sharing of
your information. In accordance with local law, your controls and choices may include:
    You may correct, update and delete your registration account.
    You may change your choices for subscriptions, newsletters and alerts. For example, you can opt-out of
     receiving newsletters and marketing emails by using the unsubscribe mechanism contained within them.
    You may choose whether we share your personal information with other companies so they can send
     you offers and promotions about their products and services by requesting that we do not do so.
    You may choose whether to receive targeted advertising from many ad networks, data
     exchanges, marketing analytics and other service providers by following the directions in the
     “Advertising” section below.
    You may request access to the personal information we hold about you and that we amend or delete it
     and we request third parties with whom we have shared the information do the same.
You may exercise your controls and choices, or request access to your personal information, by accessing
your account profile if you have an account, contacting us as set forth in Section 15 below, or followin g
instructions provided in communications sent to you. We will use reasonable efforts to accommodate your
requests and will explain when we are not able to do so. Please be aware that, if you do not allow us to
collect personal information from you, we may not be able to deliver certain products and services to you, and
some of our services may not be able to take account of your interests and preferences. If you have questions
regarding the specific personal information about you that we process or retain, please contact us. For
additional rights under applicable EU data protection laws, please see Section 14 below.
5.        What About Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies?
When you interact with the Sites and Applications, we strive to make your experience easy and meaningful. We
or our third party service providers use cookies, web beacons (including clear GIFs), Flash LSOs, and similar
technologies to track user activity and collect website and application data. We may combine this data with the
personal information we have collected from you. Currently, our systems do not recognize browser “do-not-
track” requests. . You may, however, disable certain tracking as discussed in this section (e.g., by disabling
cookies), but such disabling will impair use of the Sites and Applications.
Cookies. Cookies allow a web server to transfer data to a computer for recordkeeping and other purposes. We
and our third party service providers may use “cookies” on our Sites and Applications to, among other things,
better serve you with tailored information and facilitate your ongoing access to and use of the Sites and
Applications. There are two types of cookies: session-based and persistent cookies. In addition, we also allow

vendors to use cookies on our Sites and Applications.
    Session Cookies. Session cookies exist only during an online session. They disappear from your
     computer when you close your browser or turn off your computer. We use session cookies to allow our
     systems to uniquely identify you during a session or while you are logged in to the Sites and Applications.
     This allows us to process your online transactions and requests and verify your identity, after you have
     logged in, as you move through our Sites and Applications.
    Persistent Cookies. Persistent cookies remain on your computer after you have closed your browser
     or turned off your computer. We use persistent cookies to track aggregate and statistical information
     about user activity, which may be combined with other user information.
    Third Party Cookies. We may also engage third parties to track and analyze non-personally and
     personally identifiable website data and to serve advertisements. To do so, we may permit third parties to
     apply cookies to users of our Sites and Applications, where permitted by law, and, subject to your right to
     opt-out through the Network Advertising Initiative and About Ads (as discussed below). We use the data
     collected by such third parties to help us administer and improve the quality of the Sites and Applications
     and to analyze site usage. Such third parties may combine the information that we provide about you with
     other information that they have collected. These third parties are required to use your information in
     accordance with this Policy.
Disabling Cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but if you prefer, you can edit your
browser options to block them in future. The Help portion of the toolbar on most browsers will tell you how to
prevent your computer from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a
new cookie, or how to disable cookies altogether. Visitors to our Sites and Applications who disable their web
browsers’ ability to accept cookies will be able to browse the Sites and Applications; however, many site
features, such as the shopping cart, will not function if you disable cookies. For more information on our
cookies and opt-out features, please see our Cookies Statement.
Local Storage Objects. We and our third party service providers may use Flash Local Storage Objects (“Flash
LSOs”) in order to store your Site preferences, to personalize your visit or to display content based upon what
you view on our Site. Flash LSOs are different from browser cookies because of the amount and type of data
stored. In addition, you cannot control, delete or disable the acceptance of Flash LSOs through your browser.
For more information on Flash LSOs, or to learn how to manage your settings for Flash cookies, go to the
Adobe Flash Player Help Page, choose “Global Storage Settings Panel” and follow the instructions. To see
the Flash LSOs currently on your computer, choose “Website Storage Settings Panel” and follow the
instructions to review and, if you choose, to delete any specific Flash LSO.
Web Beacons, Pixel Tags and Other Technologies. We may use web beacons, such as clear GIFs, web
bugs or pixel tags, which are tiny graphics with a unique identifier similar in function to cookies. In contrast to
cookies, which are stored on your computer’s hard drive, clear GIFs are embedded invisibly on web pages.
We may use clear GIFs in connection with our Sites and Applications to, among other things, track the
activities of website visitors, help us manage content, and compile statistics about website usage. We and
our third party service providers also use clear GIFs in HTML e-mails to our customers, to help us track e-
mail response rates, measure the success of our marketing campaigns, identify when our e-mails are viewed
and track whether our e-mails are forwarded. For more information on the types of such tracking
technologies we use, please see our Cookies Statement.
Site Analytics. We use automated devices and applications, such as Google Analytics, to evaluate usage of
our Sites and Applications. We also may use other analytic means to evaluate our Sites and Applications . We
use these tools to help us improve our Sites and Applications, performance and user experiences. These
entities may use cookies and other tracking technologies to perform their services. We do not share your
personal information with these third parties. For the privacy policies and mechanisms for opting out of
Google Analytics, please see https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout.
Third-Party Ad Networks. We may use third parties such as network advertisers to serve advertisements on
our Sites and Applications. Please see the section entitled “Advertisements” for additional information about
our practices and your choices with regard to receiving such advertisements.
Advertisements
We display advertisements on our Sites and Applications. Some of the advertisements are based on the
collection of personal information and others are based on the collection of aggregate information. Please see
the bottom of this section for opt-out information.

We use third parties such as network advertisers to serve advertisements on our Sites and Applications.
Network advertisers are third parties that display advertisements based on your visits to our Sites and
Applications and other websites and applications you have visited. This enables us and these third parti es to
target advertisements to you for products and services in which you might be interested. Third party ad
network providers, advertisers, sponsors and/or traffic measurement services may use cookies, JavaScript,
web beacons (including clear GIFs), Flash LSOs and other technologies to measure the effectiveness of their
ads and to personalize advertising content to you.
These third party cookies and other technologies are governed by each third party’s specific privacy policy,
not this one. We may provide these third-party advertisers with information about your usage of our Sites and
Applications and our Services, both personally identifiable and non-personally identifiable information.
You may opt-out of many third-party ad networks. The website
http://www.networkadvertising.org/optout_nonppii.asp provides information regarding this practice by
Network Advertising Initiative (“NAI”) members, and your choices regarding having this information
used by these companies, including how to “opt-out” of third-party ad networks operated by NAI
members. You also may contact About Ads at http://www.aboutads.info/choices/ for information about opting
out of targeted advertising and your choices regarding having information used by About Ads member
companies, including how to “opt-out” of third-party ad networks operated by About Ads members. Opting out
of one or more NAI members or About Ad members (many of which will be the same) only means that those
members no longer will deliver targeted content or ads to you, but it does not mean you will no longer receive
any targeted content or ads on our Sites and Applications or other websites and applications. You may
continue to receive advertisements, for example, based on the particular website that you are viewing. Also, if
your browsers are configured to reject cookies when you visit this opt- out page, or you subsequently erase
your cookies, use a different computer or change web browsers, your NAI or About Ad opt-out may no longer,
be effective. Additional information is available on NAI’s and About Ad’s websites and applications accessible
by the above links.
6.         Children and Privacy
Our Sites and Applications are not designed for children under 13 and we do not knowingly collect information
from children under 13.
7.         Data Security and Integrity
The security, integrity and confidentiality of your information are extremely important to us. We have
implemented technical, administrative and physical security measures that are designed to protect personal
information from unauthorized access, disclosure, use and modification. From time to time, we review our
security procedures to consider appropriate new technology and methods. Please be aware though that,
despite our best efforts, no security measures are perfect or impenetrable.
8.         Data Transfers, Storage, and Processing
If you are located outside of the United States, please note that information we collect will be transferred to
and processed in the United States. By using our Sites or Applications, you consent to the transfer and
processing of your information in the United States, which does not have data protection laws that provide
the same level of protection that exists in countries in the European Economic Area (EEA) or your country of
residence. Your consent is voluntary. If, however, you do not consent, then we may not be able to provide
you with our Services or Applications.
9.         Third Party Links (Including Individual University Sites)
At times, our Sites and Applications may contain links to other third party websites. Any access to and use of
such linked websites is not governed by this Policy, but, instead, is governed by the privacy policies of those
third party websites, and we are not responsible for the information practices of such third party websites. In
addition, you will see links on the Pac-12.com website to individual Pac-12 member institutions websites,
which manage ticket purposes to sporting events and other activities. Each of those individual websites are
separately operated and maintained and governed by their own privacy policies. We are not responsible for
the information practices of these Pac-12 member institutions websites. In addition, certain of the content
streaming services offered through our Sites and Applications require you to register with your third-party cable or
satellite provider. Any information you provide to register for such services is subject to the privacy policies of

such third-party providers; we are not responsible for their information practices.
10.        Privacy Policy Changes
From time to time, we may change this Policy to accommodate new Services, Applications, technologies,
industry practices, regulatory requirements or for other purposes. We will post such changes on the Sites and
where feasible notify users through the Applications and e-mail addresses in their accounts with us.
11.        Terms and Conditions
Your use our Sites or Services, as well as any dispute over privacy, is subject to this Policy and our Terms and
Conditions, including applicable limitations on damages and the resolution of disputes.
12.        Special Information for California Consumers
If you are a California resident, California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits you to request information
regarding the disclosure of your personal information by certain members of The PAC-12 Entities to third
parties for the third parties' direct marketing purposes. With respect to these entities, this Policy applies only
to their activities within the State of California. To make such a request, please send an email to
privacy@pac-12.org
CA Privacy Rights
Pac-12 Enterprises
ATTN: Legal Department
360 Third St., 3rd Floor
San Francisco, CA 94107
privacy@pac-12.org
In your request, please specify the member of the Pac-12 Entities to which your request pertains. If no member
is specified, we will treat your request as pertaining to Pac-12 Enterprises.
13.        Data Retention
As a general rule, your personal information will not be stored longer than permitted by applicable law or longer than
necessary to fulfil our purposes for processing your personal data, which are stated above in the section “How we
use your personal data, unless we are required or believe it necessary to keep such information legal, accounting,
audit or back-up purposes, such as to respond to claims. For example, if you sign up for our newsletter we will keep
your email address for as long as you wish to receive the newsletter. If you opt-out of receiving the newsletter, we
will no longer use the email for that purpose, although we may retain the address if necessary for compliance
purposes.
14.        Special Information for EU Data Subjects
For those persons whose personal information is subject to the protections of the European Union General Data
Protection Regulation (“EU Law”), we rely on the following legal bases for processing of your personal information: (1)
to provide our Services or perform our contracts or legal obligations with you. For example, we collect your personal
information to be able to provide and authenticate you as user of the Pac-12 Now App; (2) if we have received your
consent, such as your consent to use your email address to send you newsletters. You may withdraw that consent
at any time, provided such withdrawal does not affect our use of your personal information prior to such withdrawal;
and (3) _as necessary for our legitimate interest in providing the Services and Applications where those interests do
not override your fundamental rights and freedom related to data privacy.
If your Personal Information is subject to the protections offered by EU Law, you may:
     Access, correct, update or request deletion of your personal information at any time by accessing your account
      online or by contacting as set forth in Section 15 below;
     Object to processing of your personal information, ask us to restrict processing of your personal information or
      request portability of your personal information as provided under EU law;
     Withdraw your consent at any time if we have collected and process your personal information with your consent,
      provided that such withdrawal will not affecting any processing conducted prior to receipt of the withdrawal;
     Complain to a data protection authority about our collection and use of your personal information.

To exercise any of these rights please contact us in accordance with the contact details set forth in Section 15 below.
Please note that if you are not entitled to the protections of EU Law, these rights do not apply to you.
15.      Comments and Questions
If you have a comment or question about this privacy policy, please contact us at: privacy@pac-12.org or Pac-
12 Enterprises, ATTN: Legal Department, 360 Third St., 3rd Floor, San Francisco, CA 94107.
